Should we look over?
>> Wait.
>> Oh, I can see him.
>> He already started.
>> Yeah, he already started climbing.
He's already like
You can see Wait, wait.
>> No, he's behind us.
>> Yeah, he's already higher than that.
>> No, no, you missed it.
>> Yeah, I'm waiting for him to get past
the tree.
>> I know the stupid tree is in the way.
>> But I think we're going to go back
there.
>> Oh, look. Do you see that thing with the
rope? It's actually
>> It's not him.
>> No, no, what is it?
>> It's a camera, bro.
>> Oh, do you see Alex? I can't
>> I can't see him.
>> Oh!
>> Oh my god.
>> He's so much higher than that.
>> It tells that he's in that high when he
is.
>> Bro, he's
>> Wait, do you see him?
>> Oh, I know why he's wearing red because
he's
to stand out.
>> Wait,
um I want to take some videos.
>> I just took a video.
>> I think that's it.
>> He's so good.
>> [cheering]
>> Wait, did he beat you?
>> Why did he wave to me?
>> Wait, did he wave to us?
>> Dude, no, are you still here?
>> He raced us.
>> I thought you were going to film it and
then he was filming like that.
>> Yeah, we're only going to be in
>> No, he's not going to take any time.
>> He's pretty fast.
Look at the kid.
That would be so cool.
No no no.
How is she going to get